Fatma!
Stop... stop...
What is happening here?
What is happening?
Osman Bey.
Osman Bey, right.
You will tell me what is happening.
Or I will kill you!
Be careful where you aim your arrow, Osman Bey!
You are the one at the tip of my sword, Hatun.
You should be careful first.
Father stop! Stop!
Stop! Don't, father!
Brother, drop your sword!
-My Bey...
Father, it was not Esenbike
Hatun who raided the tribe!
Holofira... Holofira...
Are you alright?
-We are...
We are, don't worry.
It was Ulugan, father.
Esenbike Hatun saved our lives.
If it wasn't for Esenbike Hatun, no
one could have survived in the tribe.
Is that so..
So she protected you, huh?
We arrived on time and wanted to save everyone.
I sent Sargun after that traitor Ulugan.
Osman Bey, don't worry.
He will pay for what he did for sure.
This is nothing yet, Ulugan.
Osman and his stupid herd behind him...
...will suffer in agony at the
tip of the sword of Esenbike...
...whom they see as their savior.
They will beg for their lives.
Kayi's people always show...
...gratitude to those who
approach with goodness...
...and furor to those who come with evilness.
Don't worry.
They are badly injured...
They haven't been in peace
for a long time, Osman Bey.
Ending this hardship, poverty...
...and landlessness...
...depends on you.
Tomorrow is the last day for you to pay the tax.
Come and say yes to me...
...and we'll forget about the tax.
We will be relatives then, not enemies.
Let us draw strength from
each other, not blood and death.
Esenbike Hatun!
Where is Ulugan?
We killed some of his nokers but...
...we lost Ulugan's trails.
Surely the day will come when he will
kneel before me and beg for his life...
...and lose his life while begging.
Who will kneel before whom
and who will beg for mercy..
Time will show us that.
We'll meet of course.
We'll meet at iftar tonight.
We will.
I have come to the frontiers
with thousands of nokers.
And thousands more are on their way here.
If you stand next to me...
...no one in this world can defeat you.
Are we going to be relatives or enemies?
Think carefully, Osman Bey.
We will follow Esenbike.
Okay my Bey..
You are swinging your sword in vain, Bala.
We both know that you cannot kill me.
What I will do to you
will make you suffer even more, Sofia.
You will
give my daughter to me!
You cannot escape from me!
We're retreating. Come on.
Sofia.
We'll see Ulugan, Sargun.
I have things to tell him.
We should watch our back then, mother.
Nokers!
You join the ones coming
after us and wait together.
Whoever comes from the tribes, we should know!
-And nobody will pass beyond here.
-As you order, my Bey!
My Bey, where are you going?
-My Bey, did we lose the tribe?
-Don't worry.
The tribe is safe.
Ulugan and Esenbike are playing against us.
Now it's time to ruin their game.
My Bey, do you think their
capturing Ulugan was just a game?
Time to go!
-They're coming!
-Damn it, Hristo.
-Where are the watchmen?
-Near the horses. A little ahead!
Sofia!
You can't go anywhere. You
have to give me my daughter!
They are standing ready for us, my Bey.
Esenbike is predicting all of our moves.
And she keeps raising obstacles.
No matter what they do to
stop us, we will break them.
But we'll do it quietly.
Come on, prepare your arrows.
Release.
My Bey, they're running away to inform Esenbike.
-Ride and follow them!
-Let's go.
Soldiers, stall them!
I said you can't go anywhere, Sofia.
You'll die before you meet
your daughter, huh, Bala?
-We'll see that when it's time.
-Soldiers, attack!
Come on, brothers!
Well..
You were going to inform your master, huh?
They'll do it if they keep standing, brother.
But they won't be able to.
The Righteous!
We'll continue on foot.
Osman took the bait.
Now he's resting quietly in his
tribe and healing his wounds.
If Osman is quiet,
...he must be planning a storm.
But I won't wait for the storm to break out.
I'll do what I do.
I don't want any mistakes
or disobedience, Ulugan.
All the nokers and
commanders in the frontiers...
...won't do anything without my permission.
-Otherwise...
-Otherwise?
Otherwise what, Esenbike Hatun?
Otherwise what?
Finish your words so I can say mine.
Otherwise the ones making
mistakes will be punished with blood.
-Good job, hatun. Come on.
-Come on.
Sofia
Sofia!
The soil will be watered
with your blood, Shahzade.
Only Allah knows that.
You're struggling in vain, Bala.
Halime will never remember you.
We'll see what when it's time, Sofia.
Gonca!
-Gonca, are you alright? -I'm fine.
You never leave me alone!
-Always, always. Let's go.
-Let's go.
You have to speak.
Sofia!
Hristo, we are retreating!
Keep running, Sofia!
You're going to bring Halime to me.
-Are you alright?
I'm fine. She thinks she's escaped.
-But we'll follow her like her shadow. Come on.
-Bala Hatun.
Thanks to Allah, I found you.
Osman Bey is waiting for you.
-What's the matter, mother?
-Ulugan attacked our tribe.
-What?
-Help us, my Allah.
What happened?
Esenbike repelled Ulugan.
She's coming to dinner.
Osman Bey is waiting for me.
Alaaddin, Gonca. You go after Sofia.
I'm going to the tribe.
We'll watch their every step, mother.
We'll never come back before we
find a lead about my sister. Don't worry.
Be careful, Alaaddin Ali.
-Go now.
-As you order, mother. Let's go, Gonca.
Come on, we're going to the tribe.
Come on.
-Let's go!
You will punish with blood
whoever makes a mistake, huh?
You heard me, Ulugan.
My Bey, we killed all the watching nokers.
Once again, they didn't surprise me.
All the demons are united
and marching to one target.
I'm Ulugan, one of the greatest
commanders of Mongolians.
Our mighty Khan Olcaytu set a target for me.
I'll follow him.
I will.
To some point, though.
Say what you have to say, Ulugan.
I'm telling you to hurry up, Esenbike Hatun.
Before I defeat Osman with my sword
...you should finish the game you call peace.
No. You have to be patient, Ulugan.
You'll swing your sword Osman only for a game.
You'll force him to ally with me.
When Osman has to have an agreement with me.
When Osman has to have an agreement with me,
...all his people will see me as the savior...
...and all Turkmen Beys appearing
before me will show respect to me.
We'll get Osman isolated.
When all of our army marching to the
borders of Kayi now arrive in the frontiers,
...then we will hit him hard.
You demon.
When she approached us with
the peace, she had an evil plan.
Yes. We'll make them pay
for getting united against Turks.
I will ruin Esenbike's evil plans.
My lady, we should examine your wound.
You should have take measures
before the wound was opened.
You should have brought more soldiers.
Not to get exposed, I tried...
-Shut up, Hristo!
Bala survived today.
Both Osman and Bala..
...will fall into my clutches again.
Come on, faster.
We're going to Akhisar.
Keep running, you snake.
When we meet my sister,
we will take care of you.
Come on.
Look at our situation in our own land.
I don't know if there is even worse.
Salute Esenbike Hatun.
Welcome.
You've honored me, Beys.
-Thank you.
I invited you here to say..
...the oppression is over.
You'll be embraced by the
mercy of the Great Ilkhanid State.
How will that happen while Ulugan
is storming around, Esenbike Hatun?
Ulugan is just a tiny bit
compared to the Ilkhanid State.
He will definitely be punished.
What do you want from us then, Esenbike Hatun?
I saved the family of Osman Bey
who you call the Protector of Frontiers...
...from Ulugan's attack a short time ago.
Soon, he will make peace
and pledge loyalty to me.
That's not the whole story, of course.
He'll either pay taxes to me...
...or make his daughter marry my son...
...and become a relative of mine.
I expect Turkish Beys to pledge loyalty as well.
Did Osman Bey...
...accept these terms, Esenbike Hatun?
Ilbay Bey is right. Will Osman Bey bow to you?
As Ilbay Bey
...accepted to stay under our wings...
...to protect himself...
...from burning in the fire of Ilkhanid State...
...Osman Bey will accept our offer as well.
I brought peace to you...
...not war.
Now..
...tell me.
Whether Osman Bey is by
my side or not on this path...
...will you stand by me?
Your intention is good, Esenbike Hatun.
I understand that you will not
prosper through oppression.
Therefore, your path is my path.
I stand with those who protect
the oppressed, not the oppressors.
We are with you, Esenbike Hatun.
Thank you, Beys.
Thank you.
Osman Bey Secret Tents
Allah...
-My Bey. -Orhan.
What is the situation, my Bey?
Just as we predicted.
Those two traitors are working together.
She pretended to be our savior
and had Ulugan raid our tribe, huh?
-They will pay for what they have done.
-Don't worry.
This will be handled today.
We will take an eye for an eye.
What are you thinking, my Bey?
While I waste Esenbike's time at iftar, you
will defeat the incoming reinforcement army.
-As you order, my Bey.
But do not forget...
...this noker unit is not like the looting ones.
These are warrior nokers
who can fight with swords.
We are not equal to them in numbers.
That's why, at the end of this road,
we can become veterans or martyrs.
Being a veteran is an honour, reaching the
shahada is the highest position for us my Bey.
Whoever comes, whether
with fire or a mace, we will...
...fulfill the duty you gave us, God willing.
Thank you.
I know.
When the end of the road is martyrdom, you
do not hesitate to sacrifice your lives.
My Bey, we will not reveal ourselves right?
-No.
You will disguise yourselves as those dogs
but you will make those dogs kill each other.
We will reduce their numbers and
make Ulugan and Esenbike enemies.
When Esenbike is attacked by Ulugan...
...she will not be able to
swallow her bite in front of me.
But my Bey, there is one more
thing we must be careful about.
We should not kill each other
under the guise of those dogs.
You are the leader of this fight, Orhan.
You will take care of that.
May our war be blessed.
-Live long, my Bey.
-Thank you my Bey.
Brother, do you have any dog disguise?
Do you think you are funny?
My Shahzade, find a solution to this matter.
Otherwise, I can take this Boran's
heart out with my double swords.
Don't be so quick to decide brother.
Bala Hatun.
Yes, my daughter...
You know, that woman escaped from you...
What will happen now?
She is not in our hands for now, my daughter.
But this will not stop me
from finding my Halime.
Sofia is your enemy.
Why do you believe her words?
Meryem.
Look, my daughter.
I wrote the prayer inside
this with my own hands.
I put this around my daughter's neck.
My Halime is alive. I know.
And we will find her.
What if..
...she is lying again to hurt you?
Mothers can feel, Meryem.
Who knows...
It's so little but..
...even I can feel it in my heart.
If my Bala mother is saying that
Halime is alive, she must be alive.
Right..
My Fatma..
My beautiful daughter, are you alright?
Mother..
I am afraid.
What if they a play a game? What if they take...
-Don't you say that!
While I, your father and
your brothers are here...
...no one can touch you,
my beautiful-eyed daughter.
Don't.
Mother...
We are preparing iftaar for our enemies
The devil says, "Put poison
in their food, and kill them all."
My daughter...
Responding to the tyrant's cruelty with
the same moves makes us tyrants too.
Our path is the path of
justice. We rule with justice.
Mother, our enemies are not like us.
They took Halime from us
when she was a little child.
They don't believe in right or wrong.
We show them mercy, but they don't show us any.
That's why Fatma, we won't be like them.
What makes us who we are
is not our sword, but our hearts.
With the rule of justice, we keep
the oppressed peaceful, right?
And killing with poison is easy.
But defeating the enemy means
making them kneel before justice.
The snake entered its nest.
There is no other way.
I will go into the snake's
nest to find my sister's trail.
My Shahzade, a Byzantine unit is approaching.
Good.
Who are you? What do you want?
The ruler of the frontiers...
...the servant of Islam...
...Osman Bey's son Shahzade Alaeddin
So, your executioner.
You lost your mind, Turk. You
made a mistake by facing me alone.
Is that so?
Now I'm scared.
Then let's do this...
Allah is Eternal!
Allah is Righteous!
I will kill you.
I don't have a life to
give to a dog and a jackal.
Come.
Hide the dead.
Put on their clothes.
We will enter Akhisar.
The ones coming are the
strongest nokers of the Mongol army.
Welcoming this steel-wristed
unit is my lion-hearted son's duty.
For your trust, I will get over the mountains
and bring that unit here, my Mother Sultan.
May your path be open and
your mind strong, my son.
Zolzaya.
Have the gifts for Osman been prepared?
As you ordered, sir.
The carts are loaded.
We cannot go to the iftar with empty hands.
Right Ilbay?
Sure.
But it's Osman.
We will go to him with a cart full of gifts.
But he can put poison in
front of us instead of food.
I'll go to the iftar, Ilbay.
Not you.
Osman's insolence has no limits, Esenbike Hatun.
Ilbay is trying to say it's
good to take precautions.
When he has the chance, he will poison you.
Osman's death will be beneficial
for everyone on frontiers.
I know well what is benefical
and not beneficial for whom, Ilbay.
I also know why you're so angry.
Let's go, Zolzaya.
Near Akhisar Castle
Alps, you two will enter the castle with me.
As you order my Shahzade.
And you will wait with Gonca Hatun at the lodge.
"As you order my Shahzade.", huh?
Look at me.
Stop there...
Trickster Hatun...
Why did you wear these clothes?
Where do you think you are going?
I will go wherever you are going. Scholar.
No we won't do that, my Gonca.
I said I am going into the enemy's den.
-It's too dangerous, you can't come.
-It's dangerous, huh?
Where did we meet, Alaeddin? Did you forget?
I remember, I remember for sure.
The crazy daughter of Germiyan, Gonca Hatun.
-Crazy?
-Yes, crazy, totally crazy.
Alaeddin.
Calm down.
I will come with you!
Alright. Come then.
My Hatun's word is the last word now.
Right...
It won't be bad..
We will remember the old days.
Let it be as you said. Trickster Hatun.
Alaeddin!
Let's go then, Trickster Hatun, get on.
Come on then. Everybody should be careful.
You wait here. We may need
to send a message to my father.
-As you order, my Bey.
-Here we go.
Are you ready, Trickster Hatun?
-I'm ready. Scholar.
-Here we go! May Allah help us. Let's go!
You have many daughters and
girls. Are you still dealing with this?
Everyone is busy, Osman. So I'm doing this.
You invited the hatun to
iftar. We have to offer food.
Look at me. Look.
-Now you are the wife of Osman the Dark!
-What?
It looks good on you, though.
-Stop making fun of me.
-No.
-It really looks good.
-Osman.
I don't know if it was a good
move to invite her to iftar, but...
...Fatma seems scared.
No. Nobody can scare my daughter.
I invited the enemy here so I
could know what she intends to do.
Yes, but that hatun wants to play games.
I'll show her how the game should be played.
-Let's go. -Go where?
-We need to go, Bala. They're waiting for us.
-Who?
Oh... Fatma, Ulgen
Check this cauldron.
-Let's go.
-Osman, there is much to do here.
Well... I'm taking you away.
There is much to do.
-We're going.
-Going where?
You'll see when we arrive.
-Who is waiting? -Come with me.
My Bey.
-We're going, huh?
-I'm taking you away!
Won't you really tell me?
-No.
You're really taking me away, huh?
Well, you were so ready to come with me.
Well... I said yes to you years ago.
That means you are ready.
Yes, I am.
If you are going to death
and we're going together,
...I will never object.
As long as you are with me,
...neither the path nor the death can scare me.
Is this it? This is it.
Osman, I'm really curious now.
Bala, just wait. Just wait.
Be patient. Don't be so curious.
Look. Did you find my headscarf?
Yes. I also found you.
Do you know who brought it to me?
-Who?
Alaca.
-Osman.
-Yes, Alaca.
Alaca... My Alaca
My Alaca.
Osman.
My girl. My girl.
Well, Bala..
I thought I lost you.
Then Alaca brought you to me.
After Begum wounded her that day,
...I was afraid to hear what happened.
-I thought I lost my girl.
-No. Don't worry.
I made her wait to stand ready before you.
Your girl is strong.
Very strong.
Yes. My Alaca, are you alright?
-You're good.
-She's good.
Don't worry.
She'll be even better.
In fact, even better than before.
Then...
When Alaca fully recovers.
...promise me that we will have a race.
Oh... You say so?
Did you hear that, Iltutan?
Then you have my word. You have my word.
Thanks to you, we're taking
back all what we lost, Osman.
We'll take back our daughter too.
And our tribe too.
Alaaddin is following Sofia now.
She'll definitely leave traces. Definitely.
God willing.
Let's go, come on.
Bala.
-Let's go.
-Let's go!
Come on, Alaca!
We'll kick up a dust shortly, Boran.
Are you ready, brother?
Boran, I'm talking to you. Speak.
Cerkutay Bey, I'm Yusuf.
-Yusuf?
-Yes, Yusuf.
Where is Boran?
I don't know.
Boran? Boran! Boran...
You aren't. Where is Boran? Where is he? Boran?
Boran
Brother.
What's your problem this time, Cerkutay?
Look, brothers. I can't recognize anyone.
If I see you in the battlefield,
I may slaughter any of you!
Oh no.
-How will we prevent that?
-Right, brother.
-How can we prevent that?
-Alps.
What will we do with them, my Shahzade?
Wrap these around your arms.
So you won't confuse us with the others.
We're going to slaughter
everyone without a red rag.
Samil.
Brother.
Brothers, wrap your rags tightly.
Those without a rag around
their arms can't survive my wrath.
Come on, alps.
-Come on.
-Is it good?
-It looks perfect.
My strong nokers!
Welcome!
We maintained order in the
eastern lands with our bloody swords!
We spread all around.
The western lands will be the next!
Are you ready to....
...make them kneel and bow to us?
We're ready! We're ready!
What do you promise to looters in this world?
Blood! Blood! Blood!
-Welcome, Esenbike Hatun.
-Welcome.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
We weren't expecting you so early.
No problem.
I wanted to arrive in the daylight and
hand out gifts to people before iftar.
-Welcome, Osman Bey.
-Thanks.
-Welcome, Bala Hatun.
Coming early was a good idea, Esenbike Hatun.
Finally, we'll get to know each other.
Finally, Bala Hatun.
You must have heard enough about me, though.
We don't judge before we make sure.
Well..
You should rest till iftar.
-Welcome, my Bey.
Thank you.
My Shahzade, Sargun and nokers are coming.
Let them come.
-Cerkutay Bey.
-My Shahzade.
Show us a good cryout!
I will yell so loudly that Esenbike
Hatun will hear from our tribe.
Alright.
Alps, get ready.
Attack for Ulugan!
Ulugan.
What are you doing?
Ulugan will be victorious!
You'll pay for this, Ulugan.
You're attempting to kill me and my army, huh?
Easy, Sargun.
-Nokers!
-You have days to live.
Attack!
Die already!
Marcus was supposed to
bring the goods. Where is he?
He is too sick.
So they sent me instead.
But I'm starving.
I want to finish this
business and eat until burst.
Alright, you can pass. Open the gate!
You excluded us, but...
...Ulugan is going to make you pay for this!
My nokers... Ulugan
You're going to pay for this.
-We have to go
commander.
Come on, we're retreating!
Two heads are better than one!
Look how they scattered.
Now Sargun will go and hold
onto his mother's skirt and cry.
As long as the Turk's iron
fist and brave Alps exist...
...they will only find peace under the ground.
Brothers..
...fighting like these
infidels was really difficult.
While killing them one by one, I had a hard
time holding myself from screaming Takbir!
Be careful, brother.
For sure...
For sure the day will come
when we will announce the oneness of God.
We will shout so loudly that...
...the whole world will hear us, God willing.
God willing.
My Shahzade, you're wounded.
It's not important, Shamil. It's
not important, Alps. Let's go.
We'll return to the tribe. Let's go there
before that Sargun dog. Let's go there...
...and inform my Bey.
Let's go.
I will..
...never accept an alliance...
...between a Mongol and a Turk.
I will kill them!
Then what will we do, Ulugan?
For now..
...we will do what Esenbike said.
Let Osman lower his guard first.
Then we will put our black swords...
...into his heart and take his heart out.
Osman Bey Secret Tents
Finally we met, Bala Hatun.
It is an honor.
You protected the lives of
our people and our loved ones.
We are honoured, Esenbike Hatun.
We saw and heard.
Neither our people will spare their
gratitude nor the Beys you have invited.
With you standing against Ulugan, it is
clear that everyone will gather around you.
Right, Osman Bey. True.
Those who stand by justice always gather unity.
But you know...
...what I really wish is to unite with you.
My son, Sargun wanted to join the invitation.
But he went to welcome the reinforcement units.
So the reinforcement units have arrived, huh?
Where are your Shahzades, Osman Bey?
Our children also have their duties...
...although those may not
be as important as your son's.
Is this invitation for your
gratitude towards me only?
Or will you try to make me give
up the conditions I set by saying...
..."I cannot find the gold to pay the
tax and I will not give my daughter."?
On the contrary, before
the time you gave us is up...
...I will give you the tax you want tomorrow.
That's why we invited you here.
They are guarding Sofia's door.
Tell me. Scholar. What will we do now?
-We will take over the shift.
-How? Where are you going Scholar?
What are you doing here? Who are you?
We are taking over the shift by
the order of Commander Hristo.
There is still time before the change. Why?
I don't know. But...
...actually...
...according to what I've heard..
...damned Turks escaped from Sofia again.
Maybe that's why.
Don't tell anyone..
...but both were very angry.
The shift is yours.
Sweet words can even bring
a snake out of its den, Hatun.
-And your stubbornness...
-Alaeddin, be quiet! Be quiet!
Fear, Hatun. Fear.
Fear rules people.
These soldiers know Sofia's
anger well. They are scared of her.
They ran away to avoid
being punished by her anger.
Of course they ran away.
We broke our fast.
We are now feeling better.
Now answer my question, Osman Bey.
Where did you find all that gold to pay the tax?
Ayaz Bey...
He will bring the gold he
obtained from the spoils...
...from the tribes outside our borders.
-Ayaz Bey, huh?
-Ayaz Bey, yes.
Ayaz Bey.
What happened, Esenbike Hatun?
Why are you frowning?
Shouldn't you be happy? You
will get the tax you wanted so much.
I never thought you would
find it in such a short time.
What makes me happy..
...is not just the tax...
...but the fact that there
will be peace between us.
Good. Good.
Tomorrow, we will pay the tax at
Guzelsu on the Karacahisar borders.
-Can I come in, my Bey?
-Come in Orhan Bey.
Peace be upon you.
-Peace be upon you too.
My son
Tell me, did you fulfill your duty?
-Did you succeed?
-Sure.
For sure we succeeded.
May Allah bless you.
May Allah bless you too, my Bey.
-It was an important duty apparently.
-Yes.
Right.
It was an important duty, Esenbike Hatun.
-My Bey can I come in? -Come in Boran.
My Bey, Esenbike Hatun's son Sargun is here.
Why are you keeping him outside? Let him in.
Let him in.
As you order, my Bey. Alps.
Mother..
What happened, Sargun?
We were attacked when we
met with our reinforcement units.
Who dares to do this?
Ulugan.
It was Ulugan's nokers who attacked us.
Do you know?
Even in the swamps that swallow people...
...flowers bloom that attract
a person at first glance.
Allah Allah.
Now, did you think of
flowers in this state, Alaeddin?
No, don't look at me
like that. It's all your fault.
-My fault? -Yes.
-What did I do? -What else can you do?
Even in clothes dirtier than a swamp...
...you shine like those flowers, Hatun.
But I don't like you like this.
Allah Allah, why is that?
I like you! Why don't you like me?!
I don't. I don't like you. What will you do?
-Does a person ever say that to her husband?
-Yes. -The dog Hristo is coming.
-Is Sofia alone?
-Yes.
I asked him.
He is sick. Commander Hristo.
He vomits. He doesn't speak much.
Take him to the healer.
As you order, Commander Hristo.
Well done, Gonca.
Hristo.
Come.
Bala will never stop.
She will look in every hole to find Halime.
I will leave no trails.
Is there such a trail, ma'am?
The Priestess who raised Halime, Lucia...
...lives in a secret monastery. That woman...
...will never speak, Hristo.
Tomorrow, you will go there...
...and kill Priestess Lucia.
-As you order, ma'am.
Bala...
...will never find Halime.
Never.
There is someone who knows who Halime is.
They will kill her to silence her.
No one will stop me...
...from finding my sister, my Halime.
So nokers shouted Ulugan's name...
...while they were attacking, is that so?
-They ambushed us.
Those traitors took their measures.
They suddenly showed up before us.
We fought back, but we retreated
when we lost too many men.
So the one who was with us yesterday...
...killed our nokers without mercy today.
Fate is turning our friends into enemies...
...and enemies into friends.
You did many things though.
You chained Ulugan in front of his nokers.
You came to our tribe and stood against him.
You are right...
Ulugan is blinded by his courage then...
This is really courageous.
He will pay for what he did, of course.
-Of course he will.
Either you will do it or us.
He will get killed by dark steel.
If you'll excuse me...
...I will go to Kayi tribe
and check my casualties.
Bala Hatun, you hosted us well. Thank you.
Kayi always hosts its guests as they deserve.
Shahzade Orhan.
You seem tired.
Yet, it should be you who
looks tired after the defeat.
Right Sargun?
We'll see, Orhan.
We'll see each other often.
Whenever you want.
We can meet anytime you want. Safely.
Remember.
Tomorrow, at Guzelsu...
...we will pay the tax.
There is someone who knows where Halime is.
But Allah knows in which monastery she is.
I'm chasing a chance for my sister, Gonca.
When Hristo leaves, we will
follow him and find that woman.
Alaeddin.
Sofia will do everything to kill
that woman. You know that, right?
I will not let those tyrants who separated
my sister from her family have another joy.
My mother must be worried now.
But when they hear this good
news, they will be very happy.
Yes, they will.
When we make that woman talk
and my sister reunites with her family...
...that joy will last forever, right Gonca?
-Yes.
Come on.
Ulugan Mongolian Camp
Kneel, Altuga!
What do you think you're doing, Esenbike?
I didn't come here to ask questions.
I am here to make you
pay for what you did Ulugan!
My units were ambushed.
My most trusted men were killed.
When they attacked, they
shouted your name, Ulugan.
When the arrival of your units...
...would benefit me the most,
why would I break that power?
How can you believe this, Esenbike?
I surely didn't do this.
While Osman hosted you in his tent...
...he did this behind your back apparently.
You didn't do it.
But Osman planned such a game that...
...when they raided the place...
...they left traces everywhere
that pointed to you.
Traces that you cannot prove otherwise, Ulugan.
I told you that you can't...
...fool Osman with tricks, Esenbike.
He deserved to die.
Let's go kill him.
-No.
Osman is playing a game against us.
We're playing a game against him too.
Osman already accepted paying
taxes. What you said won't happen.
How did he find the gold?
How is he going to pay the tax?
Tomorrow, he'll take the
amount I demanded as the tax...
...from Ayaz Bey and bring it to me.
So he won't have to make
his daughter marry my son.
I mean... He thinks so.
I will ambush Osman...
...and take the gold from him.
So he won't be able to keep his promise.
When he can't pay the taxes
...he will have to make
his daughter marry my son.
That's when the big game begins.
Osman's rebellious head will bow to me.
And then nobody will be able
to stand against Mongolians.
Well... They can break us neither with the
burning dagger they stick into our heart...
...nor with the wounds they open in our chests.
We will cauterize our wounds...
...and always keep walking in the path of Allah.
-God willing, my Bey.
-For sure, my Bey.
But what about the ones who abandoned the
path of Allah and the existing fight of Turks?
Well... The Beys who went to Esenbike...
Although they know Mongolians
slaughtered people in the frontiers.
...how could they believe their
tricks and pledge loyalty to Esenbike?
I don't understand.
Everybody knows what we did to
those who abandoned our cause, my Bey.
As you taught us once, my Bey.
A state is as powerful as the
punishment of the those who betray it.
Nobody should doubt our power.
Any treason against us will be
punished with a sword, my Bey.
Esenbike thinks Beys are the
preys and she herself is the predator.
She laid a trap and drew them on her side.
But we are neither preys nor predators.
We are a high tree under whose shadow...
...they are running.
We want to provide a state with whose
light it will enlighten the whole world!
Definitely, we will punish the treason.
But we should also remove
the curtains before their eyes.
You said right and enlightened our path, my Bey.
Being a state requires us
to get rid of our ambitions...
...and getting united by being patient
even if it feels too heavy for nafs.
It's such an order...
...that the whole world will
be a homeland for Turks.
It's an order that will bring justice
to continents with our swords.
Whoever shows teeth
against us will lose their teeth.
Whoever shows their claws will lose their claws.
We will get united.
For the future of Turks and Islam,
...we'll always keep the
fire of resurrection high.
And we'll stand up
together for the sake of Allah.
-God willing, my Bey.
Now we need to pay the tax to Esenbike.
-Ayaz Bey.
-My Bey.
Go to your tribe tomorrow.
Take the carts loaded with chests...
..and come to the border of Karacahisar.
There we will meet Esenbike.
As you order, my Bey.
Now..
Everybody get to work.
Okay my Bey.
-Son.
-My Bey.
My Bey.
It's from Shahzade Alaaddin
Bey. A messenger brought it.
Is it good news, my Bey?
Sofia's dog, Hristo.
The woman who raised Halime...
He's going to visit her tomorrow.
Gonca and Alaaddin...
...are following him.
Meryem.
Bala Hatun, I kept quiet when
I saw you performing prayer.
Ulgen Hatun has sent me.
Thank you, girl.
It looks beautiful.
We've got one step closer to Halime, Meryem.
Is it good?
It's hot but it smells very good.
It smells good because you touched it.
Come here, girl.
Wait, it's too hot.
Come on, come on.
I'm full.
You can't go before it's finished, Halime. Come.
Halime, wait. My girl... Halime!
You have to finish the soup, Halime.
Come here.
Halime, you have to finish the soup. My girl!
Don't make me run! Well..
I got you.
I'll eat if you turn me.
You want to play, huh?
Come here.
My Halime...
My beautiful, daughter.
You want to play, huh?
You want o play?
My beautiful girl.
Meryem.
Meryem, are you alright?
Meryem, are you alright? Do you hear me? Meryem?
Mother.
My girl.
My girl. My girl, Meryem.
Meryem, Meryem.
My Allah... Oh..
Meryem! My girl... Meryem
My girl, do you hear me? Are you alright?
I'm fine. I'm fine.
I was dreaming.
I saw my mother.
You must have got exhausted.
Don't go anywhere today. Rest in your tent.
Come on, my girl.
Mother, is there something wrong?
It's alright, my girl.
Meryem is like a little sick.
-Ulgen, take care of Meryem.
-Alright. Come here.
Don't worry, Bala.
-I should finish the preparations.
-Mother.
I'll go with you. I can help you in the temple.
No, my girl. You're pregnant. You stay.
-Mother.
I know them well. I speak their language.
-Let me go with you.
-Fine.
You can.
Let's go find Priestess Lucia.
-Alright.
Let's finish the preparations.
Lucia?
Oh my tribe...
Oh... Oh..
My cause.
My issue.
Jackals raiding my dreams.
They built obstacles on my ideal.
Help my, my Allah.
Help me, my Allah.
O The Most Merciful of the merciful.
Oh Almighty Allah..
I'm here for Your help.
I'm here for Your help, my Allah.
I bow to You, my Allah.
I'd gladly sacrifice my head for You, my Allah.
I see Your Grace.
I see Your help, my Allah.
We are just a few, my Allah.
They are too many.
For coins.
For fame.
For glory.
The number of those abandoning
Your path has increased, my Allah.
The number of those holding Your
divine rope has decreased, my Allah.
We are just a few.
Only a few.
We're helpless.
Allah.
O Creator!
For the sake of...
...our Prophet, peace be upon you, who said
that the companions of the poor...
...are Allah and His messenger.
Let this poor man..
...be Your companion.
Help me make my few many.
Help me make up my shortage, my Allah.
Don't leave me...
...to heathens, my Allah.
My Allah, give me strength.
Give me power.
During this tough fight.
...make me and those
supporting me victorious, my Allah.
My Allah, let me take back my tribe...
...and protect my state.
Help me spread Your glorious
Name all around the world, my Allah.
We're ready to move, my Bey.
God willing, we will have a
double victory today, my Bey.
God willing, God willing.
Those who weaving the webs of evil will see...
Even if they bend the wing of Turks,
...they can never break it.
Here we go.
Osman has set out, Ulugan.
Finally.
The gold he desires so much...
..will be strained with Osman's filthy blood.
Are you going to kill him, Ulugan?
What about Esenbike?
-She wants peace...
-Peace...
...is provided when the
strong one destroys the enemy.
Today, Osman's lifeless head...
...is going to kiss under my feet.
Am I going crazy?
Why is this happening to me?
Meryem.
Are you alright?
-I'm fine, Ulgen Hatun.
-Don't stand up. Don't.
I promised Bala. You
have to rest until she's back.
But I'm fine.
If you insist, I'll send Ghazi here.
He'll destroy you with his nagging.
-Alright. I won't stand up.
-Okay. Lie down.
-Lie down there. Have a good rest.
-I won't stand up.
You're comfortable?
Have a good rest. I'll be back.
Ulgen Hatun.
Bala Hatun mentioned a priestess.
-Do you know who she is?
-Yes.
The priestess who raised Halime.
Lu... Lucia or..
A foreigner name like that.
Sitting up again? Lie down!
I'll be back.
Lucia raised me not Halime.
She's my aunt's only confidant.
I have to let my aunt know.
But if she goes there
...Bala Hatun will be there.
They'll kill each other.
Yes, Holofira insisted on coming with us.
I wouldn't have let her, but...
I'll be alright with you, mother. Don't worry.
I can help you a lot in the monastery.
-That's right.
But we don't know which monastery it is.
Someone's coming. Come on.
Soldiers, we won't stop until we reach Odios!
Even I can't save you
from Sofia this time! Let's go!
Photinodios. I know that place.
Let's go.
We have to reach there before them.
We should make her speak
before those dogs kill her.
-Holofira, do you know a shortcut? -I do.
But not far away from the way Hristo is using.
Alps, you follow Hristo.
-Stop them from reaching the monastery.
-As you order, Bala Hatun.
We should reach there
quickly through the shortcut.
Let's go.
-Let's go.
-Come on, come on.
Alaca. Come on, my girl.
Go, Osman.
I will spill your blood...
...into the hearts of all
the mountains of this world.
Ulugan, why don't we take his
life now? What are we waiting for?
Wait.
Let's see the gold first...
So we will take both his life and his wealth.
After taking Osman's life...
...those who will want to take his
revenge must also be left helpless.
Let's go. Let's go without being noticed.
My Mother Sultan.
I said she was a shepherd's daughter, but...
...I didn't expect her to be like this.
-Fatma Hatun...
She is very beautiful.
Very smart, very merciful. -Yes.
I want this marriage as much as you do now.
My only fear is that Osman Bey won't agree.
Until now..
...what have we wanted that
we haven't taken, my lion?
I will leave Osman Bey no
choice but to give his daughter.
Fatma will eventually become your bride.
This woman will use us
and kill us. What will we do?
It's not that easy, Begum.
I suffered heavily to get here.
I won't give up my position, you, or my life.
What's your plan?
We will play the biggest game.
We must get there before Hristo.
If that woman speaks, we
will find Halime soon. Alaeddin!
We will make it,
mother, we will, come on!
Soon...
I am coming my Halime! We will come,
my daughter, we will meet. Let's go!
Now we will change the path.
We will go this way to get rid of them.
-As you order my Bey.
-Alps!
You will come after us and
remove the shoeprints. Come on!
Osman is playing games again.
He never lets go of his suspicion.
Let him do his best.
All his efforts are in vain.
Let's surround him.
My Bey, Ayaz Bey is coming.
Peace be upon you.
Peace be upon you, too.
All the gold is here, my Bey.
You stood by us in this
difficult time, Ayaz Bey.
Thank you, give us your pardon.
-It's yours, my Bey.
Osman
You have to ask me first!
But you will pay for it with your life.
I had a dream. Your lineage will
end and your land will be ruined.
Just because a jackal had a dream, it
doesn't mean the wolves will go extinct.
There were many like you in
these lands before. Don't worry.
My steel sword will bring your death.
Then let's settle our account.
Ayaz.
Take the chests.
-As you order, my Bey.
Attack!
May Lord Jesus protect you. Priestess Lucia.
We came to see her.
We weren't expecting any guests today.
It was especially requested to be kept secret.
We came all the way from the Monastery of
Saint John in Constantinople just for this.
So, Saint John. Who sent you from there?
Priest Hodegon.
He told us to see Priestess Lucia.
We have important things to tell her.
Forgive us, ma'am.
Here.
They killed Marcus and took his place.
The man who brought the goods
said he was sick. They left at night.
Idiots!
Did you believe this?
If they left, they must have
learned what they wanted.
Damn it.
They are after Hristo.
-We're leaving.
-As you order.
Ulugan... I will do terrible things to you...
Don't tire yourself. You
have a few breaths left.
Nokers! Protect Ulugan, come on!
Ulugan! You can't fight
in this condition. Get up!
-Give me my sword!
-Leave, Ulugan!
-I'll keep them here, go!
-My Bey!
Ulugan, come on! Nokers!
Protect Ulugan, come on!
My Bey!
The dog Ulugan is running away!
Brother.
-Come, don't betray your people while dying.
-Altuga.
You're still trying to play games.
But now the game is
over. This is the battlefield.
Now I will teach you this.
You will teach me, huh?
You will teach me.
Ulugan!
Today, even these beech trees
you trust so much will not protect you
Nokers!
Come on! Keep them there!
Where are you going?
Priestess Lucia is waiting for you, come in.
Soldiers, you stay here.
Hurry, Alps
Now this is the end of
the way for you all, infidels!
Come!
Our swords will be watered with blood!
Give up already.
You have no moves left to make!
Now...
...it is time for you to go to Ucmag.
I can go to Ucmag but...
..you..
...will face Erlik Khan's furor, brother.
Come on!
Traitor brother...
Kill me, brother.
Kill me and send me to our mother Meral Hatun.
I will tell her that..
...her own son, my brother
Cerkutay sent me there.
Kill me.
Don't show me mercy, brother! Kill me!
You are weak, brother.
You are still weak.
Alps!
Gather here!
Cerkutay Bey.
Brother... what happened?
I couldn't kill him.
I couldn't..
I could not move after he
said my mother's name...
Cerkutay Bey.
Don't worry.
What you are going to do is not easy.
Alps.
Is everyone alright? -We are alright my Bey.
We are, my Shahzade.
-Come on then.
We will go to my father.
Stop there... Stop there...
Many had the chance of
suffering from my slap before you.
Now it's your turn.
I won't fall easily.
You cannot defeat me, Osman.
-You will fall!
You will fall in such a way that...
My name is Osman Bey! I came to this world...
...to make those like you
pay for what you have done!
I came to this world to stamp the mark of
justice that will never fade on your forehead!
You will fail.
Is that so?
Almighty Allah...
...sent me here so I could
fight against those like you.
But I swear to Allah...
...until I kill you and others like you...
...I will never stop.
Now the era of Ulugan is over.
I have never seen you before. Who are you?
You actually know me.
For God's sake, what is happening?
-There is nothing to be scared of.
I am Osman Bey's Hatun, Bala Hatun.
You are not surprised.
You were waiting for me then.
Where is my daughter?
I knew this sin would not let me go.
I've been waiting for you
for ten years, Bala Hatun.
Priestess Lucia, God will never forgive you.
You separated a mother and a child.
You committed the greatest sin!
Now is not the time to confess the sins!
Tell me where my daughter is.
I can't tell you that...
Sofia won't let me live.
You will die anyway!
I am here to save you.
Sofia sent Hristo to have you killed.
I will see Priestess Lucia.
I brought news from Sofia.
They are already here.
Sofia exposed her secret.
Now she wants to kill
everyone who knows her secret.
It's your turn.
Speak before your death comes.
Tell us where Halime is. We don't have time.
-I don't know.
I am telling you that Sofia will kill
everyone who knows her secret!
You decide.
Tell him that I left to go to the village
and that he should wait for a while.
She..
Just like you...
...she is fearless and beautiful.
Where is she now?
She raised her like her own daughter.
She never left her side.
She loves her like her mother...
Snake!
When will she come
back from the village?
I don't know.
Sofia is coming!
Damn it!
Why did that woman come here?
Let's go and find my mother.
We have to leave this place immediately. Come
Tell me, where is my Halime?
Where does she keep her?
She is not Halime.
Alaeddin.
Mother, Sofia found it out. She
is coming here with her soldiers.
We need to leave now.
Sofia is coming for you.
You will come with me if you want to live.
Which way should we go? Tell us!
Are there any other exits besides the main gate?
Bala is here!
Close all the gates! Hurry!
What are you saying, Sofia?
Idiot!
While you are waiting here...
...Bala is making Lucia speak inside!
Come on!
Around Guzelsu
Last night, he tricked us.
I want to cut off Osman's
head when he comes, but...
Don't worry, son.
It will be as we wish.
When Ulugan takes the gold from Ayaz,
...Osman will get his tail between his
legs and make his daughter marry you.
Esenbike Hatun, Osman's coming.
What's the cart behind him?
-Did he... Did he get rid of
Ulugan and bring the tax, mother?
-Osman Bey.
-As we agreed.
I've brought the tax.
What? Weren't you expecting this?
-Ha, Esenbike Hatun.
-Of course, I was.
Let me see the gold which
is the price of our peace.
Let's see then.
Open it.
What does this mean, Osman Bey?
Are you playing a trick?
Do you have a death wish?
Kanyumaz! Samil!
Bring.
Ulugan.
Yes, Ulugan.
I'm thirsty for the life of your
rebellious commander Ulugan.
This door. But it hasn't been used for long.
Come on.
I'll look after you until I find Halime.
Her name isn't Halime.
-She doesn't remember her name, you or anything.
-What's her name?
Bala!
Her name is Poena.
What I've brought for you isn't the gold.
The tax I pay you is the head...
...of the dog called
Ulugan you were looking for.
Stop.
Nokers!
That sword will never touch Ulugan!
Otherwise you can't survive here.
Beys!
Come here.
Come and see.
See this hatun..
...who was supposed to protect our
tribe and people from Ulugan's tyranny.
Just wait.
Wait for a while.
I won't kill you so easily.
Are you afraid, Osman?
Are you afraid of the powerful Mongolian army...
...who would come for you if you killed me?
You're right.
Yes... But still
...we will come for you.
Where are you going, Ulugan?
-Oh...
Just wait.
We have a matter to settle.
You got tricked by the wolf?
While you thought I was seeking the gold,
...I was seeking you.
Osman.
Yes, Osman.
Of course, Osman.
Did you think I didn't notice the
game you and Esenbike were playing?
I'm the ruler of these lands.
These lands belong to me.
I know even the worms inside
the throat of the bird flying here.
Just wait.
Take him.
Send a message to Beys.
-Everything will be revealed.
-Get up!
You said your way was separated from Ulugan.
But it's you who killed the
innocent people in the hidden tribe.
I'd rather lose my head than
bow to this treacherous hatun!
Don't worry. You will lose your heads.
The head to be lost today...
...will be this dog's head.
And then, Osman?
What do you think will happen then?
Don't worry.
You will be the next.
Turn around and see my power, Osman Bey.
You think you can stand against me
with a few alps and mindless Beys?
No.
You can't do this.
Game is over.
Let Ulugan go.
-Or...
Or what?
Or I won't kill only you
but also all of your kin!
I'll leave you lonely and desperate, Osman Bey.
I can be lonely but never mistaken.
Even if I die
...those who follow me
will never let you get away.
Tell me... Have we ever
let the evil ones get away?
Say your final words.
If you do this.
...you'll be wiped out.
Mongolians who destroyed
you even for a messenger...
...will wipe you out of the history
for their glorious commander Ulugan.
You came here and trampled on my land.
You and people like you.
Whoever comes after you
and messes with my nation...
...will live the same fate.